And ladies and gentlemen, this is the
final award under the insurance category
and this is the winner for the
outstanding digital CX life insurance.
Congratulations to Manu Life
Philippines. Please welcome Chief
Marketing Officer
to the stage.
[Music]
Hi, good evening everybody. Uh, thank
you digital banker. It's it's really an
honor to be here. Uh on behalf of entire
Manual Life and specifically Manual Life
Philippines. Uh very very glad to accept
this award. It's uh a long time making
digital customer experience is something
that we really invest in and with
decisions made easier lives made better
for our customers goes at the back of
human- centered design and really a very
uh laser sharp focus on customer
experience that makes Manual Life
Philippines uh the leader in net
promoter score at plus 85 and we are
extremely proud of that and this is on
behalf of the entire team uh not just
Manolife Philippines uh but globally man
life.
[Music]